ched.gov.ph 2018-07-28

# Privacy Notice - CHED

The right to privacy is well stated in the 1987 Philippine Constitution particularly in Sections I, III, VI, VIII and XVII of the Bill of Rights. It is also safeguarded by several provisions of the Civil Code and the Revised Penal Code, among others. As such, R.A. No. 10173 or the _Data Privacy Act of 2012_ was enacted to uphold the citizens’ right to privacy through responsible handling of data. In compliance, the Commission on Higher Education (CHED) recognizes the right to privacy of its internal and external stakeholders.

Personal Information collected by the Commission through this Portal will be used primarily to give the site’s editors and administrators an idea of how the CHED stakeholders use the Portal and what information they are looking for in the portal. Information collected from users will not be used for marketing or commercial purposes.

We collect personal information in this portal when users visit our site and send feedback using the CONTACT US button. The personal information collected will be used primarily to address inquiries or concerns sent to Commission using the CONTACT US button. The CHED Technical Staff in-charge of answering and/or responding to queries or concerns may endorse a user’s message, along with his or her information to the appropriate CHED office for appropriate action. If in any case you wish to exempt your information from this practice, please indicate as much in your correspondence.

Further, this site contains links to and from websites of government departments and other organizations. This privacy policy, however, only applies to the CHED Portal as other websites may have privacy and user policies which are different from the Commission’s.

For further questions and/or clarifications, please coordinate with:

Commission on Higher Education  
HEDC Building, CP Garcia Avenue  
Diliman, Quezon City  
info@ched.gov.ph
